Fuck. Hang on.
حسناً، مهلاً.
Fuck it's--
"ساعدونا على حفظ تاريخ مقبرة (بانهيل)"
Shit. Give me your hand.
تباً. أعطيني يدك.
- It's higher than it looks. Be careful. - It's not that high.
إنه أعلى مما يبدو. انتبهي.
All right, Min. It's fine. It's not that hard.
أجل، حسناً يا "مين". لا بأس. إنه ليس صعباً لهذه الدرجة.
It's just higher than it looks. Ready?
إنه أعلى مما يبدو فقط، جاهزة؟
Hands off, Min.
أبعد يديك يا "مين".
Shit.
تباً.
For fuck's sake.
- بحق السماء. - لماذا تنوح الآن؟
Fucking ripped my coat.
مزقت معطفي اللعين.
I've ripped my coat completely.
مزقت معطفي بالكامل.
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm fine. Why? You see anyone?
- هل أنت بخير؟ - أجل، أنا بخير. لماذا؟ هل ترى أحداً؟
- No, can you? - No.
لا، هل ترين أحداً؟ لا.
Taverner's voice mail.
بريد "تافيرنر" الصوتي.
In the car you said you'd tell me.
قلت في السيارة إنك ستخبرني.
So, what did she mean about Charles's death?
إذاً، ماذا كانت تقصد بحديثها عن موت "تشارلز"؟
Read the room, will you? Is now really the time?
هل يمكنك تفهّم الوضع الحالي؟ هل هذا الوقت المناسب؟
It's Lamb.
إنه "لامب".
"Minuisa."
الثنائي "مينويزا".
You've got a key?
هل معك مفتاح؟
I told you to get Struan.
طلبت منكما إحضار "ستروان".
The Dogs got to him just before us.
وصل المحققون إليه قبلنا.
- Did they see you? - Yo.
- هل رأوكما؟ - أهلاً.
Cartwright?
و"كارترايت"؟
Went to try and wake Sleeping Beauty.
ذهب ليحاول إيقاظ الجميلة النائمة.
Sid. She's in a coma and is a beauty.
"سيد". هي جميلة وفي غيبوبة.
Or was, till she got shot in the head.
أو كانت، حتى تعرضت لطلقة في وجهها.
Oh, Jesus, Ho.
يا للهول يا "هو".
Dog rolled up, so I split.
ظهر محقق لذا هربت.
We gotta go.
علينا الذهاب.
Taverner will pick us off one by one.
ستحاول "تافيرنر" القبض علينا واحداً تلو الآخر.
Find someone to turn.
ستحاول إقناع أحدنا بالخيانة.
She and Black had a plan.
كانت لديها خطة مع "بلاك".
Now that's gone to shit, she'll try and play it as Slough House gone rogue.
بعد فشل الخطة، ستحاول إظهار الأمر كأن "سلو هاوس" الخونة.
And what about the boy? What happens to Hassan?
وماذا عن الفتى؟ ماذا سيحدث لـ"حسن"؟
If he's not dead already, he soon will be.
إن لم يمت بالفعل، فسيموت قريباً.
You're a fucking dickhead, Roddy.
أنت وغد لعين يا "رودي".
I remember where I saw Alan Black.
تذكرت أين رأيت "ألان بلاك".
He was meeting with Taverner.
كان في لقاء مع "تافيرنر".
All right, go back. What were they doing?
حسناً، تذكر ذلك. ماذا كانا يفعلان؟
Talking at her gym café.
كانا يتحدثان في مقهى قاعتها الرياضية.
It came back to me when I saw Sid
تذكرت ذلك عندما رأيت "سيد"
because she took the piss out of me for following Taverner.
لأنها كانت تسخر مني لتعقبي لـ"تافيرنر".
They were meeting secretly.
كانا يتقابلان سراً.
But it's your word against hers.
لكن ستكون أقوالك في مواجهة أقوالها.
Yes, but I was following her for surveillance training.
أجل، لكنني كنت أتبعها لتدريب المراقبة.
So I took a photograph.
لذا التقطت صورة.
Well, do you have it?
هل هي معك؟
No, not yet.
لا، ليس بعد،
But I think I know where there might be a copy.
لكن أظن أنني أعرف أين قد نجد نسخة.
A copy?
نسخة؟
This is hopeless.
ميؤوس منه.
Well, it would certainly seem that way.
يبدو الأمر كذلك.
Look.
اسمعوا.
but this feels like a big moment,
لكن أشعر بأن هذه لحظة مناسبة،
and if it all turns to shit, I might not see any of you again.
لأنه إن فشلنا، فقد لا أرى أياً منكم مجدداً.
You're fucking useless. The lot of you.
أنتم كلكم عديمو الجدوى.
Working with you has been the lowest point in a disappointing career.
كان العمل معكم أسوأ شيء في مسيرتي المهنية المخيبة للآمال.
Right.
حسناً.
Cartwright, you're with me.
"كارترايت"، سترافقني.
But wait, what do we do?
لكن مهلاً، ماذا سنفعل؟
Well, try not to get caught for as long as you can.
حاولوا تجنب إلقاء القبض عليكم لأطول وقت ممكن.
My money's on about 30 minutes.
أراهن بأنكم ستصمدون 30 دقيقة.
Well, we can try and save Hassan.
يمكننا محاولة إنقاذ "حسن".
That'd be a sure way to get him killed.
هذه ستكون طريقة مؤكدة لضمان قتله.
Go lock yourselves in a toilet somewhere.
اذهبوا واختبئوا في مرحاض في مكان ما.
What a wanker.
يا له من وغد.
- Where are we going? - To go and get that photo, you dickhead.
- إلى أين سنذهب؟ - لمحاولة الحصول على الصورة أيها الوغد.
Back there, that's you goading them into action, right?
كنت تحاول تحفيزهم على فعل شيء ما، صحيح؟
Fuck no. I meant every word.
لا حتماً. قصدت كل كلمة قلتها.
Right. Just checking.
صحيح. كنت أتأكد فقط.
Fucking Christ.
بحق السماء.
Police are still frantically searching
ما زالت الشرطة تبحث بشكل محموم
for the whereabouts of the hostage Hassan Ahmed,
عن مكان الرهينة "حسن أحمد"،
whose kidnappers have threatened to behead him
الذي هدد خاطفوه بقطع رأسه
at sunrise this morning around 6:30--
مع شروق شمس اليوم الساعة 6 ونصف...
You hear that?
هل تسمعان؟
So they're still expecting us to do that thing that we're not--
ما زالوا يتوقعون منا فعل الشيء
we're not fucking doing.
الذي لن نفعله حتماً.
Nothing about the dead spook.
لم يتحدثوا عن الجاسوس الميت.
Maybe they haven't found the body yet.
ربما لم يجدوا الجثة بعد.
They'll have found the body. With you two screaming
لا بد أنهم وجدوها بسبب صراخكما
like a pair of little girls, someone will have called it in.
كفتاتين صغيرتين. لا بد أن أحدهم أبلغ الشرطة.
You know why it's not on the news, right?
تعلمان لماذا لم يتحدثوا عنه في الأخبار، صحيح؟
They wanna bury it. And us.
يريدون إخفاء الخبر والتخلص منا.
An MI5 agent involved in a kidnap plot. They don't want people talking about that.
عميل من المكتب الخامس متورط في خطة خطف. لا يريدون أن يتحدث الناس عن ذلك.
Nah. We are gonna die resisting arrest, boys.
لا، سيقتلوننا في محاولة الإفلات منهم.
So the way I see it is we may as well have some fun first.
لذا أرى أنه يجب علينا الاستمتاع أولاً.
Chop-chop.
لنقطع رأسه.
Fucking hell.
يا للهول.
- So what? - Just said that.
- وبعد؟ - قلت ذلك.
So what?
وبعد؟
See any lights?
هل ترى أي ضوء؟
- Second floor, maybe. - Did you leave them on?
- ربما في الطابق الثاني. - هل تركت النور مضاء؟
I don't remember.
لا أتذكّر.
- Well, think. - I don't know.
- فكّر. - لا أعرف.
You were there too. Why didn't you check?
أنت كنت هناك أيضاً. لماذا لم تتحقق؟
Because I've earned the right not to.
لأنني نلت حق ألا أضطر لفعل ذلك.
Well, it looks clear.
يبدو المكان خالياً.
Doesn't mean to say the place isn't swarming with Dogs.
هذا لا يعني أن المكان لا يعج بالمحققين.
Or a clean-up team for the body or a trap?
أو فريق لتنظيف آثار الجثة أو فخ؟
Well, you better go in and find out.
من الأفضل أن تدخل لتكتشف.
I'm going in alone, am I?
سأدخل بمفردي، صحيح؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Thanks.
شكراً.
What is the latest we know about Hassan Ahmed?
ما آخر ما نعرفه بخصوص "حسن أحمد"؟
Well, time really is of the essence now.
أصبح الوقت حرجاً الآن،
But we've had no further updates from either the Metropolitan Police
لكن لم تصلنا أي تحديثات من شرطة العاصمة
- or the security services… - That poor boy.
- أو قوات الأمن... - ذلك المسكين.
- …with regards to the release… - How can you eat?
- ...ما يتعلق بتحرير... - كيف يمكنك أن تأكل؟
…of Hassan Ahmed.
..."حسن أحمد".
Relax. Dogs are nowhere near.
استرخوا. المحققون ليسوا هنا.
You hacked the Dogs' comms?
هل اخترقت اتصالات المحققين؟
Snuck into their kennel, muzzled them bitches,
اخترقت مكتبهم وقيّدت هؤلاء الأوغاد
- stole their bones. - That's so wrong.
- وسرقت المعلومات منهم. - هذا تصرف خاطئ.
Whatever. They're outside our homes and waiting for us.
لا يهم. إنهم ينتظروننا خارج منازلنا.
Waiting for us to use our phones and credit cards or passports.
ينتظرون أن نستخدم هواتفنا وبطاقات ائتماننا أو جوازات سفرنا.
So, we just hole up in here for the rest of our lives, do we?
هل سنختبئ هنا لما تبقى من عمرنا إذاً؟
Right. We're fucked then.
صحيح. قُضي علينا.
Can't track me.
لا يمكنهم تعقبي.
I'm a digital ghost, so I'm fine.
أنا شبح رقمي، لذا أنا بخير.
Thanks for the team spirit, Ho.
شكراً للتضامن مع الفريق يا "هو".
You're forgetting Lamb.
لقد نسيتم "لامب".
Lamb doesn't care about us.
"لامب" لا يكترث لأمرنا.
As soon as whatever he's got planned goes south, he's gonna forget us.
إن فشلت الخطة التي وضعها، فسينسى أمرنا.
That's not true.
غير صحيح.
The thing Charles always said about Lamb--
كان "تشارلز" يقول عن "لامب"...
Charles?
"تشارلز"؟
You hurt his joes, he'll never stop coming for you.
إنه إن تأذى عملاؤه، فلن يقف ساكناً.
And the thing, for Lamb, there's nothing worse than not being able to get even.
وفي نظر "لامب"، أسوأ شيء هو عدم الانتقام.
And he's not gonna wanna lose to Taverner.
ولن يود أن يخسر في مواجهة "تافيرنر".
- Exactly. - I think he's got even more contempt
- بالضبط. - أظن أنه يكن لها ضغينة
for her than he does for us.
أكثر مما يكنه لنا.
Wow, that's a skip-load of contempt.
عجباً! هذا قدر كبير من الضغينة.
And meanwhile, we what?
وماذا سنفعل في أثناء ذلك؟
Can we talk about the ethics of this for a moment?
هل يمكننا التحدث عن أخلاقيات ذلك؟
Because if they are going to behead Hassan at 6:30 a.m.,
لأنهم إن قطعوا رأس "حسن" الساعة 6 ونصف صباحاً
as they say they are, are people really going to watch?
كما قالوا إنهم سيفعلون، فهل سيشاهدهم الناس؟
And if they do, are they not complicit?
وإن فعلوا ذلك، أفليسوا مشاركين أيضاً؟
Roddy, where are the Park on Hassan?
"رودي"، ما تحديثات "بارك" عن "حسن"؟
They've just narrowed it down to ten vehicles that have left the area.
قلصوا البحث إلى 10 مركبات غادرت من تلك المنطقة.
The one thing that we can bring to this is that we knew Alan Black,
الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكننا تقديمه هو معرفتنا بـ"ألان بلاك".
what do we remember about him?
ماذا نتذكر عنه؟
He was sent to Slough House
أُرسل إلى "سلو هاوس"
for sleeping with the Venezuelan ambassador's wife while undercover.
لمضاجعة زوجة السفير الفنزويلي في أثناء عمله متخفياً.
Apart from that.
بخلاف ذلك.
He moaned a lot. Never bought biscuits.
كان ينوح كثيراً ولم يشتر البسكويت قطّ.
- Oh, my God. - Sorry, what? We're free-forming.
- يا للهول. - ماذا؟ نقول ما يخطر ببالنا.
- There's no bad ideas here. - He was really lazy.
- لا تُوجد أفكار سيئة. - كان كسولاً جداً.
And that's better than what I said, is it?
وهل هذا أفضل مما قلته؟
Listen, he was undercover with the Sons of Albion,
اسمعوا، كان متخفياً مع "أبناء ألبيون"
so there would have been a birth certificate,
لذا لا بد أنه كانت هناك شهادة ميلاد
passport, credit cards, the full legend.
وجواز سفر وبطاقة ائتمان وتسجيل كامل.
Yeah. Deep cover's expensive.
أجل، عمليات التخفي الكاملة باهظة.
He was tight, so he definitely wouldn't want to have to front that.
كان بخيلاً جداً، لذا لم يكن يريد تحمّل تكلفة ذلك حتماً.
More than that. Taverner won't want any of it to show up on the books.
إضافة على ذلك، لن تود "تافيرنر" أن يظهر أي من ذلك في السجلات.
So he could have used an old ID.
لذا ربما استخدم مستندات قديمة.
Roddy?
"رودي"؟
If you'll give me a few minutes, ladies.
امنحوني عدة دقائق يا سيداتي.
And gentleman.
وسيد.
Ladies.
يا سيدات.
And that's another "Ho-me" run.
عملية ناجحة أخرى لـ"هو".
Meet Dermot Radcliffe.
قابلوا "ديرموت رادكليف".
AKA Alan Black.
المعروف باسم "ألان بلاك".
Legend for a football hooligan.
مشاغب كرة القدم المعروف.
Ex-forces too.
جندي سابق أيضاً.
That's catnip for British nationalists.
هذا يجتذب القوميّين البريطانيين.
Let's see what Dermot's been up to recently.
لنر ما فعله "ديرموت" مؤخراً.
Sorry, Jed. Lamb's idea.
آسف يا "جيد". هذه فكرة "لامب".
- Lamb and Standish-- - Have not been apprehended.
- "لامب" و"ستانديش"... - لم يُقبض عليهما.
- Yes, I can see that. - Lamb pulled a gun.
- أجل، أرى ذلك. - هددنا "لامب" بمسدس.
You didn't frisk him?
ألم تفتشاه؟
It was in Standish's bag.
كان في حقيبة "ستانديش".
This is them?
هل هؤلاء المجرمون؟
Fingerprints match those at the Roupell Street house.
تطابق البصمات تلك في المنزل في شارع "روبل".
They all have priors. ABH, GBH, burglary.
لديهم كلهم سوابق في إلحاق الأذى البدني والسطو.
- How we doing on the vehicles? - Still have eight to locate,
- أي تحديثات عن المركبات؟ - ما زلنا نحاول الوصول إلى 8،
but they might be avoiding roads with CCTV.
لكنهم ربما يتجنبون الشوارع بالكاميرات.
They may have swapped vehicles.
ربما غيّروا المركبة.
We're following up on all reported vehicle thefts.
نتابع كل تقارير سرقات المركبات.
- Ma'am. - Not now.
- سيدتي. - ليس الآن.
Showtime.
حان وقت العرض.
We're running out of petrol.
سينفد منا الوقود.
No.
لا.
Fuck off!
تباً!
So what? Stop at the garage.
ماذا في ذلك؟ سنتوقف في محطة الوقود.
- We're covered in fucking blood. - Bit of a giveaway.
- تغطينا الدماء اللعينة. - سيفضح هذا أمرنا.
We'll end up on the CCTV.
سيصوروننا على الكاميرات.
Shouldn't have left the balaclavas behind.
ما كان يجب أن نترك الأقنعة.
Well, we can't make the boat
لا يمكننا الوصول إلى القارب
- without petrol, can we? - Just calm down. I've got a plan.
- من دون وقود، صحيح؟ - اهدآ، لديّ خطة.
- Yeah? - We drive until we run out,
- حقاً؟ - سنقود حتى ينفد الوقود،
and then we're gonna chop his head off.
ثم سنقطع رأسه.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
ما خطبك بحق السماء؟
- Yeah, let's just think about this. - We don't have options.
- أجل، لنفكر في ذلك فقط. - ليست لدينا خيارات.
Yeah, we do. We have the option not to fucking do that.
بلى، لدينا. لدينا خيار ألا نفعل ذلك.
And have all this for nothing?
ليكون كل ما فعلناه هباء؟
While they set us up and make us look like twats and we don't even do
يحاولون الإيقاع بنا وجعلنا نبدو كمغفلين ونحن لم نفعل
the thing that we said we were gonna do.
الشيء الذي قلنا إننا سنفعله.
No, I can't have that.
لا، لن أقبل بهذا.
We'll be a fucking joke.
سنكون أضحوكة.
People need to fear and respect us.
يجب أن يخشانا الناس ويحترمونا.
They need to know that we mean what we say when we say it.
يجب أن يعرفوا أننا جادون في ما نقوله عندما نقوله.
Enough is enough, man. This is our country, and we want it--
هذا يكفي يا رجل. هذا بلدنا ونريد...
Fucking shut up!
اخرس بحق السماء!
I've had enough. Okay?
لقد اكتفيت من ذلك، اتفقنا؟
- Where'd you get that? - On the guy whose head he cut off, eh?
- من أين جئت بهذا؟ - من الرجل الذي قطع رأسه.
He said he was a spy, but you didn't check his pockets, did ya?
قال إنه جاسوس، لكنك لم تتفقد جيوبه، صحيح؟
And I'm the dumb one, aren't I?
وتعدّني الغبي، صحيح؟
You'd rather spill my British blood than his, then you're a traitor.
أنت تفضّل أن تسفك دمائي البريطانية على دمائه، لهذا أنت خائن.
Yeah.
أجل.
Get in the back. Check he's okay.
اذهب إلى الخلف. تأكد أنه بخير.
You're a fucking embarrassment, man.
أنت مصدر إحراج يا رجل.
I think he's being sick.
أظن أنه يتقيأ.
Yep. He's choking on his sick.
أجل، سيختنق بالقيء.
- Result. - Hey.
- رائع. - مهلاً.
Pull over. Chop-chop.
اركن السيارة. بسرعة.
Get out.
اخرج.
Go on.
هيا.
I said get out, now.
قلت، اخرج الآن.
Come on. Move it.
هيا، تحرك.
Just move it. Open the door.
تحرك. افتح الباب.
Right. Lift him up.
حسناً، ارفعه.
And get that fucking tape off his face.
وانزع اللاصق اللعين عن وجهه.
Fuck.
تباً.
Okay.
حسناً.
Put something in his mouth.
ضع شيئاً في فمه.
In case he screams.
في حالة أنه صرخ.
Why aren't you threatening him, you fucking pussy?
لماذا لا تهدده أيها الجبان اللعين؟
You told him you're not gonna kill him, didn't ya?
أخبرته بالفعل بأنك لن تقتله، صحيح؟
Don't fucking push me. Okay?
لا تستفزني، اتفقنا؟
Don't!
لا تفعل!
No fuel. Nowhere to go.
لا وقود. لا مكان نذهب إليه.
What's the plan now, Captain?
ما الخطة الآن يا قبطان؟
We get some petrol, right?
سنحصل على بعض الوقود، صحيح؟
We get to the boat…
سنذهب إلى القارب
- and we let the kid go. - Who's gonna get the petrol?
- وسنترك الفتى يذهب. - من سيحصل على الوقود؟
What?
ماذا؟
Have you looked in the mirror?
هل نظرت في المرآة؟
Who's gonna get out of the van?
من سيخرج من الشاحنة؟
Fuck it. Fuck it.
تباً لذلك.
He is.
هو سيذهب.
Got him. Like a rat in a trap that I will kill with a hammer.
"(تريبل دي) لتأجير المركبات"
"Triple-D Car Hire." Leeds address.
"تريبل دي" لتأجير المركبات. عنوانها في "ليدز".
Registration number?
رقم التسجيل؟
That will take a while.
سيستغرق هذا بعض الوقت.
Get me a coffee.
أحضر لي قهوة.
I need fuel for this one.
أحتاج إلى وقود لفعل هذا.
An SQL injection attack will take hours,
يستغرق الهجوم بفيروس إلكتروني ساعات،
which leaves a malware bomb as the most effective method,
وهذا يترك على أثره شفرة إلكترونية وهي الأسلوب الأكثر فعالية،
but that needs someone to open an email, so…
لكنني أحتاج إلى شخص يفتح البريد الإلكتروني...
Cheers, Standish. Double espresso.
شكراً يا "ستانديش". إسبريسو مضاعفة.
I thought you could hack anything.
ظننت أنه يمكنك اختراق أي شيء.
I can.
يمكنني ذلك.
I'm not saying I can't do it. Just that it will take some time.
لم أقل إنه لا يمكنني فعلها، أقول فقط إنه سيستغرق بعض الوقت.
How much time do you need, Ho?
إلى كم من الوقت تحتاج يا "هو"؟
Because the kid's gonna get beheaded in about two and a half hours.
لأنهم سيقطعون رأس الفتى بعد ساعتين ونصف.
I'll tell you what I can do real quick.
سأخبرك بما يمكنني فعله بسرعة.
Check your search history and tell everyone what porn you look at.
فتح تاريخ بحثك على الإنترنت وإخبار الجميع بالأفلام الإباحية التي تشاهدها.
Fine, 'cause I've got nothing to hide.
حسناً، لأنه ليس لديّ ما أخفيه.
- Don't you fucking dare. - Hey.
- إياك أن تجرؤ. - مهلاً.
- Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. - What's wrong with you?
- توقف. - ما خطبك؟
You're eight years old.
أنت تتصرف كطفل.
- Pardon? - Where's my coffee?
- معذرة؟ - أين قهوتي؟
I didn't get you a coffee. I got you the registration number.
لم أحضر لك قهوة. أحضرت رقم التسجيل.
DE15 CGK.
"دي إي 15 سي جيه كيه".
- What? How? - Well, I rang them up.
- ماذا؟ كيف؟ - اتصلت بهم.
And said what? "Do you mind breaking multiple data protection laws?"
ماذا قلت لهم؟ "هل تمانعون خرق عدة قوانين لحماية البيانات؟"
No, I said th-that I'd had an accident with one of their vehicles
لا، قلت إنني تعرضت لحادثة مع إحدى سياراتهم
and I had the driver's name, but because I was so shaken,
واسم السائق معي، لكن بسبب الصدمة
I couldn't read the registration number I'd written down.
لا يمكنني قراءة رقم التسجيل الذي كتبته.
I think the words you're looking for, Ho, and these would be a first for you,
أظن أن الكلمات التي تبحث عنها يا "هو"، وهذه ستكون سابقة لك،
are, "Well done" and "Thank you."
هي "أحسنت" و"شكراً".
It's on the list of vehicles the Park are looking for.
إنها على قائمة المركبات التي تلاحقها "بارك".
Then we need to get them to focus on that vehicle.
يجب أن نجعلهم يركزون جهودهم على تلك المركبة.
How do we let the Park know that without them tracking us?
كيف سنخبرهم في "بارك" بذلك من دون أن يتعقبونا؟
Oh, my God. Min, a kid's life is at stake.
يا للهول يا "مين"، حياة الفتى في خطر.
I know, but Lamb told us not to get caught.
أعرف، لكن "لامب" طلب منا ألا يُقبض علينا.
Can't we track it ourselves?
ألا يمكننا تعقبها بأنفسنا؟
- Stop!
- توقف!
Stop!
توقف!
Stay in the vehicle.
ابق في السيارة.
Yes, I know I'm gonna be
"أجل، أعلم أنني سأكون
I'm gonna be the man Who's working hard for you
سأكون الرجل الذي يعمل بجد من أجلك
And when the money
وعندما أحصل على..."
Stay there.
ابق مكانك.
Comes in for the work I do I'll pass almost every penny on to you
"المال لقاء عملي، فسأعطيك كل قرش"
- Move! Move! - Come on, let's go!
- تحركوا! - هيا، لنتحرك!
Move!
تحركوا!
Go. Go. Move.
هيا، تحركوا.
Well, I know I'm gonna be
"أعلم أنني سأكون
I'm gonna be the man Who's growing old with you
سأكون الرجل الذي يكبر معك
But I would walk 500 miles
لكنني سأسير 500 ميل
And I would walk 500 more
وسأسير 500 ميل أخرى..."
Can you get out of the vehicle, please, Mr. Lamb?
هل يمكنك الخروج من السيارة يا سيد "لامب"؟
No, no. I'm quite comfortable where I am.
لا، أشعر بالراحة في مكاني هنا.
These seats are lovely. And they're heated too.
هذه المقاعد لطيفة وفيها تدفئة أيضاً.
- Step out of the vehicle now. - Nah, I'm okay where I am.
- اخرج من المركبة الآن. - لا، أنا بخير في مكاني.
You go fetch your boss and tell him I've brought the car back,
أحضر مديرك وأخبره بأنني أعدت السيارة،
but we need to go over the damage waiver.
لكن يجب علينا مناقشة التأمين.
You help us get petrol, you help us get to the boat,
ساعدنا على الحصول على الوقود والوصول إلى القارب
and we will let you go. I swear.
وسنطلق سراحك. أقسم لك.
Yeah? Okay.
اتفقنا؟ حسناً.
Listen, be cool. Okay?
اسمع، اهدأ، اتفقنا؟
He's seen all our faces, man. He has got to go.
لقد رأى وجوهنا يا رجل. يجب أن نقتله.
No! Listen. Why aren't you taking me seriously?
لا! اسمع. لماذا لا تأخذني على محمل الجد؟
'Cause I'm the one with the fucking gun, remember?
لأنني الذي يحمل المسدس اللعين، أتذكر؟
He's got a point. Look, I don't like it either, but he's right.
وجهة نظره سديدة. اسمع، لا يعجبني هذا أيضاً، لكنه محق.
Please, please. I'll say I never saw your faces
أرجوكم. سأقول إنني لم أر وجوهكم
or I never heard your voices or I blanked it out from stress.
أو لم أسمع أصواتكم أو نسيتها بسبب التوتر.
Right now he'll say anything.
سيقول لنا أي شيء الآن.
My uncle's got money.
عمي يملك المال.
Proving my point.
هذا يثبت وجهة نظري.
No, straight up. My uncle's rich.
لا، جدياً. عمي ثري.
Look, your exit plan, it-- it might not work, but my uncle, he can sort that.
اسمعوا، قد تفشل خطة هروبكم، لكن عمي يمكنه حل هذه المشكلة.
- He can help you. He can make something-- - You little fucking lying rat!
- يمكنه مساعدتكم. يمكنه أن يفعل شيئاً... - أيها الوغد الكاذب اللعين!
Hey! Hey! Fucking stop it!
مهلاً! توقف عن هذا!
Your uncle.
عمك.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Islamabad.
"إسلام آباد".
Where?
أين؟
Pakistan.
"باكستان".
What the fuck use is that to us?
كيف سيفيدنا ذلك بحق السماء؟
- You get your money and you disappear. - This is such fucking bullshit.
- ستحصلون على المال وستختفون. - هذا هراء لعين.
- He's messing with ya. - Fucking stop it. I'm thinking, okay?
- إنه يخدعكما. - توقف بحق السماء. أنا أفكر، اتفقنا؟
- That should take a while. - Hey.
- سيستغرق هذا بعض الوقت. - مهلاً.
Fucking don't. Okay? Don't.
لا تفعل هذا، اتفقنا؟ لا تفعلها.
It's gotta be worth a shot, yeah.
الأمر يستحق المحاولة، أجل.
Yeah?
صحيح؟
But you're coming on the boat too, and you stay with us till we get the money.
لكنك سترافقنا على القارب أيضاً وستبقى معنا حتى نحصل على المال.
Get out of the car.
اخرج من السيارة.
What?
ماذا؟
Is this a joke?
هل هذه نكتة؟
No, it's the Proclaimers.
لا، إنهم "بروكليمرز".
Get out of the--
اخرج من...
Nick, relax. I brought the car back.
استرخ يا "نيك". أعدت لك السيارة.
You pulled a gun on me.
أنت هددتني بمسدس.
No, I delegated that. And any court of law
لا، فوّضت أخرى بذلك. أي محكمة قانونية ستخبرك بأنه يُوجد فرق بين الأمرين.
And she didn't pull a gun on you. She pulled a gun on your boy.
وهي لم تهددك بمسدس، هي هددت عميلك.
Get out of the car.
اخرج من السيارة.
Are you gonna shoot me?
هل ستطلق النار عليّ؟
- Not right now. - Yeah, well, what about one of your lads?
- ليس الآن. - ماذا عن أحد عملائك؟
Hair triggers make natural scratching posts for itchy indexes.
يبدون متحمسين للضغط على الزناد.
They're not gonna do anything unless you do.
لن يفعلوا شيئاً ما لم تفعل شيئاً.
You got my word on that. Now get out of the fucking car.
أعدك بذلك. الآن اخرج من السيارة اللعينة.
All right. Good.
حسناً، جيد.
'Cause I was wanting a little word with Lady Di.
لأنني أردت التحدث إلى الليدي "دي".
All right.
حسناً.
Just reaching for a peashooter.
أمد يدي لأخرج المسدس.
Here you go.
تفضل.
Park it downstairs.
اركنها في الأسفل.
I could murder a coffee.
كم أودّ شرب كوب قهوة.
What's the canteen like in this gaff?
ما تقييم المقصف في هذا المكان؟
Dogs en route. Stand by.
المحققون في الطريق. استعدوا.
What's your plan then, big man?
ما خطتك أيها القائد؟
Hey, you get out. You fill up the van.
اخرج واملأ الشاحنة.
Nod, nod, nod.
أومئ.
You fill up the van, and we all get the fuck out of here.
املأ الشاحنة وسنرحل من هنا.
Yes?
اتفقنا؟
Give him some money.
أعطه بعض المال.
How do you know he won't do a runner?
كيف نتأكد أنه لن يهرب؟
Hey, listen, kid. You've gotta come back.
اسمع يا فتى. يجب أن تعود.
See that lady in the front filling up?
هل ترى تلك السيدة التي تملأ الوقود؟
The one with the two kids in the car?
تلك التي لديها طفلان في السيارة؟
Hey!
أنت!
Do you see that woman?
هل ترى تلك المرأة؟
If you do anything wrong,
إن فعلت أي شيء،
I'll walk round to the back of the van, and I'll get my axe out.
فسأذهب إلى مؤخرة الشاحنة وسأخرج فأسي.
And I'll cut her kids' heads off in front of her.
وسأقطع رأسي طفليها أمامها.
Then I'll cut her head off, then yours.
ثم سأقطع رأسها، ثم سأقطع رأسك.
And you know I'll do that, right?
وأنت تعلم أنني سأفعل ذلك، صحيح؟
Yeah.
أجل.
Hey, kid. Don't fuck this up.
اسمع يا فتى. لا تفسد هذا الأمر.
Diesel, yeah?
سولار، اتفقنا؟
Knobhead. Keep your eye on him.
أيها الغبي، راقبه جيداً.
Excuse me. Hello.
معذرة. أهلاً.
- For fuck's sake. - No, no, no.
- بحق السماء. - لا.
- Fuck off. - I'm sorry, I need your help.
- تباً. - آسفة، أحتاج إلى مساعدتك.
Can't get me petrol cap back on.
لا يمكنني إعادة وضع غطاء خزان الوقود.
Maybe the attendant can help.
ربما يمكن للموظف مساعدتك.
Oh, no. 'Cause he's stuck behind glass and, you know…
لا. لأنه عالق خلف الزجاج...
- What's she saying? - …the only way I can get…
- ماذا تقول؟ - ...والطريقة الوحيدة لفعل ذلك...
Fuck this.
تباً لذلك.
…I gotta get moving again soon.
...عليّ التحرك قريباً.
But I'll--
لكنني...
But I'll, No, I'll work it out.
لكنني لا... سأتوصل إلى حل ما.
Hey, Mervin. Help the poor woman.
اسمع يا "ميرفن"، ساعد المرأة المسكينة.
Hey, look, I'm sorry about him.
اسمعي. آسف بخصوصه.
Think he'd be a lot happier. He's getting married in seven days.
ظننت أنه سيكون أسعد. سيتزوج خلال 7 أيام.
It's a stag weekend.
إنها عطلة توديع العزوبية.
Oh, God. Sorry.
رباه. آسفة.
You know, you look like that--
أنت تشبه...
You know, the-- That--
ذلك...
- You know, the fell-- - Yeah. Yeah, I know. The--
- كما تعلم، الرجل... - أجل. أعرف.
- The Pakistani boy that was kidnapped. - Yeah.
- الفتى الباكستاني الذي خُطف. - أجل.
Yeah, I get it.
أجل، أتفهّم ذلك.
Had it all bloody day.
سمعت ذلك طيلة اليوم.
But I suppose we all just look the same to you people, right?
لكن أفترض أنكم تروننا كلنا متشابهين، صحيح؟
No. No, I wasn't-- It's just 'cause I was thinking--
لا، لم أكن أقصد... هذا لأنني كنت أفكر...
Hey, I was just joking.
مهلاً، كنت أمزح.
Yeah.
أجل.
Sorry.
آسف.
How about I look at that cap for you, yeah?
ما رأيك لو بحثت عن الغطاء؟
Yeah, that'd be-- Yeah, thank you.
أجل، هذا سيكون... أجل، شكراً.
Hey. Knock that off now.
مهلاً، توقفي الآن.
I'm sorry they're up.
آسف لإيقاظهما.
- It's all right. It's not your fault. - Nah, nah!
- لا! - لا بأس. هذا ليس ذنبك.
That's really stuck in there, isn't it?
إنه عالق في مكانه، صحيح؟
There you go.
هكذا.
Hey, thank you. Have a good wedding.
اسمع، شكراً. أتمنى لك زفافاً سعيداً.
Yeah, thanks.
أجل، شكراً.
Just gotta get through a weekend with these miserable morons first.
عليّ أن أجتاز عطلة نهاية الأسبوع مع هؤلاء المغفلين البائسين أولاً.
Go and pay the man.
اذهب وادفع للرجل.
Hey, thank you again, love.
اسمع، شكراً مجدداً يا عزيزي.
Hi.
أهلاً.
She's leaving.
إنها تغادر.
There's nothing to stop him from running.
لا يُوجد ما يمنعه من الهرب.
Shit. Look at the TV.
تباً. انظرا إلى التلفاز.
Excuse me.
معذرة.
For fuck's sake.
بحق السماء.
Pump number?
رقم المضخة؟
Pump number one.
المضخة رقم 1.
It's 94.60.
الحساب 94.60.
Keep the change.
احتفظ بالباقي.
Really?
حقاً؟
Thanks, buddy.
شكراً يا رجل.
Go on. Go on, get in.
هيا، ادخل.
Shut the door.
أغلق الباب.
Good job, kid.
أحسنت يا فتى.
- Good job. - Did you get any change?
- أحسنت. - هل أعطاك الباقي؟
I gave him a tip.
أعطيته بقشيشاً.
Thank you, Nick. You can leave us now.
شكراً يا "نيك". يمكنك أن تتركنا الآن.
Three sugars. There's a love.
3 ملاعق سكر. شكراً يا عزيزي.
Alan Black's body's been found.
عثروا على جثة "ألان بلاك".
Alan Black?
"ألان بلاك"؟
It rings a bell.
هذا يبدو مألوفاً.
Ex-Slow Horse. Your man.
من الخيول الموصومة سابقاً وعميلك.
Clearly involved in the kidnapping of Hassan Ahmed.
كان متورطاً في خطف "حسن أحمد".
But you see, I remember a conversation we had on a bench earlier this evening,
لكن أنا أتذكّر محادثة جرت بيننا على مقعد أمسية اليوم،
where you told me you had a guy on the inside
عندما أخبرتني بأنه لديك عميل بينهم
who had set the whole thing up. So not my man.
دبّر الأمر كله، لذا ليس عميلي.
I have a statement from someone who saw you and Black
لديّ تصريح من شخص رآك و"بلاك"
meeting after he'd left Slough House.
في مقابلة بعد أن ترك "سلو هاوس".
Struan Loy? Bless.
"ستروان لوي"؟ هذا محزن.
You think his word stacks up against mine?
هل تظنين أنهم سيصدقونه عليّ؟
There'll be others.
سيشهد آخرون.
Standish will show.
ستأتي "ستانديش"،
And she'll turn when she knows why you're at Slough House.
وستنقلب عليك عندما تعرف سبب وجودك في "سلو هاوس".
And Moody, dead
ومات "مودي" بعد ارتكابه جريمة قتل.
I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
آسفة. ظننت أنك عرفت.
Sid Baker's gone.
ماتت "سيد بيكر".
I'm gonna make you an offer, Jackson.
سأقدم لك عرضاً يا "جاكسون".
I'm sure.
أنا متأكد.
I mean, obviously you have to have this all wrapped up
بالطبع يجب عليك حل هذه الأزمة
before Tearney lands, and I can blow the whistle on you.
قبل وصول "تيرني"، وأنا يمكنني فضح خطتك.
You don't have a whistle.
ليس لديك ما تفضحني به.
All you have is a CV littered with dead joes.
كل ما تملكه هو سيرة ذاتية من العملاء الموتى.
Well, I'm not sure your career will survive the death of Hassan Ahmed.
أنا لست واثقاً بأن مسيرتك ستنجو بعد موت "حسن أحمد".
But anyway, make your pitch.
لكن لا يهم. قدمي عرضك.
I'm sure you've got some sweetener to help me neck this absolute bullshit.
أنا واثق بأن لديك شيئاً ما ليقنعني بقبول هذا الهراء.
Sign a statement that tallies with Loy's, and that'll be the end of it.
وقّع بياناً يتوافق مع شهادة "لوي"، وستكون هذه نهاية الأمر.
You mean the end of me.
أنت تعنين نهايتي.
You'd be fired, but no charges.
ستُطرد، لكن لن تُوجه لك أي تهم.
And enough of a pension to keep you in single malts.
وستحصل على معاش يلبي احتياجاتك في الشرب.
A heavily redacted file will state that you were thinking out loud
سنكتب في ملف محجوب أنك كنت تعبّر عن أفكارك
and Black went rogue.
و"بلاك" انشق عنك.
When's Tearney get back?
متى ستعود "تيرني"؟
I mean, I'd love to run all this by her.
أعني، أودّ أن أسمع رأيها في كل هذا.
Or we can sit here and watch the Slow Horses
أو يمكننا الجلوس هنا ومراقبة الخيول الموصومة
walk in one by one and accept a job back here at the Park,
يدخلون واحداً تلو الآخر ليقبلوا وظيفة تعيدهم إلى "بارك"
while you fester in the basement
بينما تتعفن في القبو
until this is all cleared up, which I can make last a very long time.
حتى تنتهي هذه الأزمة، ويمكنني أن أجعلها تستمر لوقت طويل جداً.
And if you get lonely, I can always send Standish down.
وإن شعرت بالوحدة، فسأرسل إليك "ستانديش".
The treason charge against her will be resurrected,
سيُعاد فتح تهم الخيانة في حقها،
and this time I can make it stick.
وهذه المرة يمكنني أن أثبتها عليها.
I think I might have been bitten at the canal.
يبدو أنني تعرضت للعضّ عند النهر.
Well, it sounds like a wonderful deal.
تبدو كصفقة رائعة.
And hats off to you.
أرفع لك القبعة.
You really got me boxed in.
لقد حاصرتني فعلاً.
So print off a statement. Give me a pen.
فلتطبعي التصريح وتعطيني قلماً.
Fuck, I've just remembered.
تباً، لقد تذكرت للتو.
Yeah, there was something I meant to tell you
أجل، كان هناك شيء أردت إخبارك به
as soon as I walked in.
بمجرد دخولي.
The car that I returned.
السيارة التي أعدتها.
The one that's now parked in the basement.
السيارة المركونة الآن في القبو.
It's got a bomb in the boot.
تُوجد قنبلة فيها.
- But I would walk 500 miles - Duffy.
- "لكن يمكنني قطع 500 ميل" - "دافي".
Fuck's sake.
بحق السماء.
What's he playing at?
ما الذي يحاول فعله؟
Shit. Secure the building!
تباً. أمنوا المبنى!
Search it floor by floor! We've got an intruder!
فتشوه طابقاً تلو الآخر! لدينا دخيل!
Door!
الباب!
- Now, tell me where the file is, please. - What file? What are you even saying?
- والآن أخبرني بمكان الملف من فضلك. - أي ملف؟ ماذا تقول؟
Stop pissing around. You know exactly what I mean.
كف عن العبث. أنت تعلم ما أقصده.
Whatever it is you think I have, I don't.
أياً كان ما تظنه بحوزتي، أنا لا أملكه.
Can you just put that thing down, then we can--
هل يمكنك إبعاد هذا الشيء ليمكننا...
- Which one's the photograph in? - What photograph?
- أين تُوجد الصورة؟ - أي صورة؟
Taverner wanted me out because she knew I took a photograph
أرادت "تافيرنر" التخلص مني لأنها عرفت أنني التقطت صورة
- of her and Alan Black. - I don't know what you're talking about,
- لها مع "ألان بلاك". - لا أعرف عمّا تتحدث،
but she had plenty of reasons to want rid of you, mate.
لكنها كانت لديها أسباب كثيرة لتتخلص منك يا رجل.
- You mean Stansted? - Exactly. That's why you're out.
- هل تقصد "ستانستيد"؟ - بالضبط، هذا سبب رحيلك.
I know what she did. She got you to fuck me over at Stansted
أعرف ما فعلته. هي جعلتك تخونني في عملية "ستانستيد"
because she'd have an excuse to get rid of me.
لأنها حينها سيكون لديها سبب لتتخلص مني.
It was your fiasco.
كان ذلك إخفاقك.
Now, I'm pretty sure that she'll have asked you to destroy that photograph.
أنا واثق بأنها طلبت منك تدمير الصورة.
And I'm even more sure that you'll have kept a copy for insurance.
وأنا متأكد أنك احتفظت بنسخة لتأمين نفسك.
So tell me where they are, and then I won't shoot you straight in the face.
لذا أخبرني بمكانها ولن أطلق النار على وجهك.
Sorry, mate. You lost me.
آسف يا رجل. لا أفهمك.
Tell me where it is.
أخبرني بمكانها.
Hey!
مهلاً!
Come on, come on, come on.
هيا.
Black.
"بلاك".
Come on.
"كارترايت".
No.
لا.
All teams. All teams. Evacuate workstations.
إلى كل الفرق، أخلوا محطات العمل.
Please start approaching a secure area with passes and ID.
برجاء التوجه إلى منطقة آمنة بهوياتكم الشخصية.
This is a 1470…
شفرة 1470...
- Move! Move! - Come on! Let's go!
- تحركوا! - هيا! لنذهب!
All right, everybody out this way!
حسناً، توجهوا من ذلك الاتجاه!
Stansted.
"ستانستيد".
- Move! Get out! - Move! Move! Move! This way!
- تحركوا! اخرجوا! - تحركوا! من هناك!
Move!
تحركوا!
Stansted. Stansted, Stansted.
"ستانستيد".
Motherf-- Fiasco.
إخفاق لعين.
Yeah.
أجل.
- Clear. - Move.
- خالي. - تحركوا.
We're evacuating this area.
نخلي هذه المنطقة.
Move!
تحركوا!
- Move, move, move. - Out, out, out!
- تحركوا. - اخرجوا!
- Coming through! - Clear out!
- نعبر من هنا! - تحركوا!
Out of the way!
ابتعدوا عن الطريق!
All clear! Out! Out!
المكان خال! اخرجوا!
- Move!
- تحركوا!
Webb, we have a code 1470!
"ويب"، لدينا شفرة 1470!
- Down! - Down! On the floor.
- انبطح! - انبطح! على الأرض.
…extremely worrying, and added to the investigation…
...مقلق جداً، ويُضاف إلى التحقيق...
This is yours, I believe.
أظن أن هذه ملكك.
Yeah. Must have forgot to attach the bomb part.
أجل. لا بد أنني نسيت تركيب القنبلة.
Duffy and his men are sweeping the building as we speak.
"دافي" ورجاله يفتشون المبنى بينما نتحدث.
I assume it was Cartwright you smuggled in.
أفترض أنك هربت "كارترايت" إلى الداخل.
Nah, I thought it was helpful to test your security.
لا، ظننت أنه سيكون مفيداً أن أختبر أمنكم.
I've got bad news. Your guys are not very good.
لديّ خبر سيئ. أنتم لستم بارعين.
Put him in the basement, next to Loy.
ضعه في القبو بجوار "لوي".
You got the gist of that.
لا بد أنك فهمت المكالمة.
Yeah. Well, if my guys were as good as your guys,
إن كان رجالي ببراعة رجالك،
they'd be your guys.
فسيكونون رجالك.
Now that little interlude is over, perhaps you'd like to sign this.
بعد انتهاء هذه المقاطعة القصيرة، ربما تود أن توقّع على هذا.
Before I do that, I just got one question.
قبل أن أفعل ذلك، لديّ سؤال واحد.
Who the fuck have you just sent to the basement?
من أرسلته إلى القبو بحق السماء؟
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
- Good? - Yeah.
- أحضرتها؟ - أجل.
Oh, no. I wouldn't do that, ma'am.
لا. لا أنصحك بهذا يا سيدتي.
Fiasco.
الإخفاق.
In three seconds, I could have a dozen guns pointed at your heads.
خلال 3 ثوان، يمكنني توجيه عشرات المسدسات إليكما.
Yeah, but you won't do that.
أجل، لكنك لن تفعلي ذلك.
Because you don't want anyone to see these.
لأنك لا تريدين أن يرى أحد هذه.
Here, look.
انظري هنا.
There's you, and there's Alan Black.
هذا أنت مع "ألان بلاك".
Remember setting up the thing you're accusing me of?
أتتذكرين ترتيب المهمة التي تتهمينني بها؟
Kidnapping Hassan Ahmed in a false flag operation
خطف "حسن أحمد" في عملية مزيفة
so you could rescue him, look good and score some points.
لتنقذيه وتظهري بمظهر جيد أمام القيادة.
You did tell me all that earlier, but this is evidence.
أخبرتني بكل هذا سابقاً، لكن هذا هو الدليل.
Yeah, I've put your name in. If you'd just initial the changes.
أجل، كتبت اسمك. يمكنك تأكيد التغيرات.
Sign at the bottom.
وقّعي في الأسفل.
I met with an ex-agent. That means nothing.
قابلت عميلاً سابقاً. هذا لا يعني شيئاً.
You won't mind if we send this to Tearney then?
ألا تمانعين إذاً إن أرسلناها إلى "تيرني"؟
- And everyone else at the Park. - And Hobden, while we're at it.
- وكل عملاء "بارك". - و"هوبدن" ما دمنا بصدد ذلك.
No, no. Hobden's a kook. Send it to all the news desks.
لا، "هوبدن" مجنون. أرسلها إلى مكاتب الأخبار.
- News desks. - What do you want?
- مكاتب الأخبار. - ماذا تريدان؟
I want that kid found alive.
أريد أن يُعثر على الفتى حياً.
And you think I don't?
وهل تظن أنني لا أريد ذلك؟
I think your attention's been split between finding him and burning me.
أظن أن انتباهك منقسم بين إيجاده واستهدافي.
There are three possible vehicles. We have lost track of all of them.
تُوجد 3 مركبات محتملة، وفقدنا أثرها جميعاً.
We are doing everything we can.
نبذل قصارى جهدنا.
There's something more you could do.
يُوجد شيء آخر يمكنك فعله.
Cartwright got Hobden's phone.
"كارترايت" معه هاتف "هوبدن".
It turns out there's a certain someone he called when it all went to shit.
اتضح أنه يُوجد شخص محدد اتصل به عندما ساءت الأوضاع.
Maybe you should pay that someone a visit.
ربما يجب أن تزوروا ذلك الشخص.
Hey, this deal with your uncle, how much money we talking?
اسمع، كم المبلغ الذي نتوقعه من عمك؟
Well, name your price.
حددوا ما تريدونه.
What is he? A billionaire?
ماذا يكون؟ ملياردير؟
No, he's got businesses and lots of investments. Lots.
لا، لديه شركات واستثمارات كثيرة جداً.
Oh, yeah? Well, how come he never helped you out before?
حقاً؟ لماذا لم يساعدك من قبل؟
You was living in a right shitheap back in Leeds.
كنت تعيش في مكان حقير في "ليدز".
He said he wanted me to make my own way, like he did.
قال إنه يريدني أن أحقق نجاحي بنفسي كما فعل هو.
But he wouldn't want me hurt.
لكنه لن يريد أن يمسني الأذى.
He wouldn't want me hurt.
لن يريد أن يمسني الأذى.
Hey, listen. Listen, why would he lie?
اسمع. لماذا قد يكذب؟
Like you said, he better not be bullshitting.
كما قلت، من الأفضل ألا يكون كاذباً.
Because if there is no uncle and there is no money,
لأنه إن لم يكن يُوجد عم أو مال،
- we're gonna find out, you know? - The money will be there, I swear.
- فسنكتشف ذلك، صحيح؟ - أقسم إنكم ستحصلون على المال.
- Okay? I promise it's there. My uncle-- - Yeah, all right, all right. All right!
- اتفقنا؟ أعدكم بذلك. عمي... - أجل، حسناً!
Jesus.
يا للهول.
Look, he did well at the petrol station.
اسمع، أحسنت صنعاً في محطة الوقود.
You did.
أحسنت فعلاً.
So I'll give him the benefit of the doubt.
لذا سأثق بأنه يقول الحقيقة.
He can come with us.
يمكنه مرافقتنا.
But only if he makes me laugh.
لكن فقط لو تمكن من إضحاكي.
If he fucking what?
لو تمكن من فعل ماذا؟
He's a comedian, isn't he?
هو كوميدي، صحيح؟
Well, I say "comedian." He's never had the balls to go on stage.
أقول إنه كوميدي مع أنه لم يتحل بالجرأة للصعود على المسرح.
Come on, now!
هيا الآن!
This is your big chance. You wanna come with us, don't ya?
هذه فرصتك الكبرى. أنت تريد مرافقتنا، صحيح؟
- Roast us like on Comedy Central. - Make us laugh.
- أهنّا بشكل مضحك كما في "كوميدي سنترال". - أضحكنا.
Go on!
هيا!
- Waiting. - Okay, okay.
- ننتظر. - حسناً.
So you're the Sons of Albion, huh?
أنتم "أبناء ألبيون"؟
Just a hunch,
هذا مجرد تخمين،
but is Albion married to his first cousin?
لكن هل "ألبيون" متزوج بقريبته؟
That's just fucking rude.
هذه فظاظة شديدة.
That's the point. It's insults.
هذا المغزى منها. إنها إهانات.
Go on.
أكمل.
"The Sons of Albion."
"أبناء ألبيون"
Because "Unfuckable White Men with Daddy Issues"
لأن لقب "رجال بيض قبيحون بعقد أبوية"
doesn't quite fit on a neck tattoo, does it?
ليس ملائماً لوشم على العنق، صحيح؟
Dear me.
يا للعجب!
I guess you got what you wanted.
أظن أنكم حصلتم على ما أردتم.
A Muslim bombing.
قصف مسلم.
Now, that's good.
هذا جيد.
That is good. More.
هذا جيد. المزيد.
The Sons of Albion:
"أبناء ألبيون"
Saving Great Britain from the infidels Monday to Thursday,
ينقذون "بريطانيا العظمى" من الكفرة طيلة الأسبوع،
but can't resist a good curry on a Friday night.
لكن لا يمكنهم مقاومة تناول طعامهم ليلة الجمعة.
He's talking about us!
إنه يتحدث عنا!
- Yeah? - He's on a roll.
- أجل؟ - إنه مستمر.
You're gonna need a bigger van, mate.
ستحتاجون إلى شاحنة أكبر يا رجل.
Hey, do him.
اسمع، قل نكتة عنه.
Do him.
قل نكتة عنه.
- Go on. Go on. - Look at him.
- هيا. - انظرا إليه.
If he was any more inbred, he'd be a sandwich.
هو أوضح مثال لزواج الأقارب.
Another one! Another one! This guy! Another one!
نكتة أخرى! عن هذا الوغد!
And this one, he's so dumb, he's got a note in his underpants:
وهذا غبي جداً لدرجة أنه لديه ملحوظة في سرواله الداخلي تقول،
"Wipe arse. Use paper."
"امسح المؤخرة بالمناديل."
Hey!
مهلاً!
You're fucking funny!
أنت مضحك جداً!
He's laughing now! He's laughing--
إنه يضحك الآن!
God!
رباه!
He's laughing now? He's laughing!
من يضحك الآن؟ إنه يضحك!
Fuck!
تباً!
Now that's fucking funny.
هذا مضحك جداً.